neutralexistence.com 2014-05-27

# Privacy Policy | Neutral Existence LLC

## Privacy Policy

(“I” and “we” refers to Neutral Existence LLC and/or its owner, Adam Beazley) 

We are committed to keeping all of your personal details safe and secure. My privacy policy strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

**Personal Information Collection:**

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998). We will not pass on your details to any third party entities.

The type of information we “may” collect about you includes:

_Your full name  
Your e-mail address   
Your postal address   
Your sex   
Your height   
Your weight   
Your age   
Your personal enery usage_

Generally, this information is requested when you are joining and or using our free online social network, when you purchase any of my products, or when you subscribe to my newsletters. The information I hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that I hold about you by e-mailing us at: [Support@NeutralExistence.com](mailto:Support@neutralExistence.com). If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly.

**Email Usage:**

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to periodic company news, updates, and/or related product or service information, etc.

**Personal Information Disclosure:**

We will not use your personal information for any other reason other than to contact you. We do not sell, give away or rent your email address to any third party. If in the future, we did for any reason wish to rent, sell or use your email address for any other purpose we will ask you for your express permission first.

We will only disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: 

(a) Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Neutral Existence LLC;  
(b) Protect and defend the rights or property of Neutral Existence LLC;  
(c) Act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Neutral Existence website.

**Private Information Security**

For your safety and protection, your credit card information is not stored on our servers. Our payment gateway provider, Paypal Web Payments Pro, keeps this information encrypted and secure on your behalf.

Adam Beazley, CEO  
Neutral Existence LLC
